Life blooms like a flower
生命如花朵绽放
Far away or by the road
或许遥远，或许就在路边
Waiting for the one
等待着那个人
To find the way back home
找到回家的路
Rain falls a thousand times
雨水数千次的冲刷
No footprints of come-and-go
已经分辨不清来往的脚印
You who once went by
曾经过此处的你
Where will you belong
终将属于哪里
I feel your sigh and breath
我察觉到你的叹息与呼吸
In the last blow of wind
在风最后的呼啸之中
Not yet for the story on the last page
还未到将故事翻至末页的时候
It's not the end
所以一切还未结束
Life blooms like a flower
生命如花朵绽放
Far away or by the road
遥不可及，或触手可得
Waiting for the one
等待着那个人
To find the way back home
找到回家的路
Time flows across the world
时光流淌过天地间
There is always a longer way to go
我的旅程不会结束
Till I reach your arms
直至能与你相拥
A Madder there for you
并献上一株茜草
Up against the stream
沿着溪流向上
Waterways will join as one
无数水流终将合一
Tracing to the source
追溯着源头
No more strayed or lost
便可不再迷惘
You will see petals fly
你将看见花瓣纷飞
When lament becomes carol
当悲伤之音转而歌颂
Could you please hear my voice
请你听见我的声音
That hungers for a duo
正渴望与你二重唱
Life blooms like a flower
生命如花朵绽放
Far away or by the road
或许遥远，或许就在路边
Waiting for the one
等待着那个人
To find the way back home
找到回家的路
Time flows across the world
时光流淌过天地间
There is always a longer way to go
我的旅程不会结束
Till I reach your arms
直至能与你相拥
A Madder there for you
并献上一株茜草
Life blooms like a flower
生命如花朵绽放
Far away or by the road
或许遥远，或许就在路边
Waiting for the one
等待着那个人
To find the way back home
找到回家的路
Time flows across the world
时光流淌过天地间
There is always a longer way to go
我的旅程不会结束
Till I reach your arms
直至能与你相拥
A Madder there for you
并献上一株茜草